rebateplus.com 2011-10-21

# Privacy Policy | PlusNetMarketing

Home >> Privacy Policy

_Revised: August 28, 2008_

PlusNetMarketing, Inc. (“we” or “us”) is responsible for this web site. In connection with this web site, you may provide certain personal information, which we analyze and use in order to improve your experience on our website.

### WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We collect personal information that you volunteer during your visits to our web site. This “personal information” includes names, postal addresses, e-mail addresses and/or phone numbers. This information is necessary to process your request and to provide you with appropriate service and support. In addition, we may collect optional information that users provide, such as gender and survey responses, which are used to enhance our website and coordinate future opportunities.

Our servers automatically record information when you visit our web site, including the URL, IP address, browser type and language, and the date and time of your request. It does not attempt to capture any other information, including e-mail addresses. As a result, the only e-mail addresses that we collect are those that you provide to us in connection to your requests.

When we send marketing e-mails, our servers may record: 1) when users open the e-mails; and 2) which links contained in the e-mails they click on while reviewing the e-mails.

This site may require cookies. Cookies are used to store visitors' preferences, record user-specific information on what pages within the web site users access or visit within the web site, alert visitors to new areas that we think might be of interest to them when they return to our site, record past activity at a site within the web site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site, and customize web page content based on visitors’ browser type or information that the visitor voluntarily provides directly to us.

We understand the importance of protecting children's privacy, especially in an online environment. This web site is intended for use by adults over the age of 18, and is not intended to be used by children, is not directed to them, and does not knowingly collect information from anyone under the age of 13.

### HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

We use the information that you provide on this site to: improve the content of our web site; to customize the content and/or layout of the site for each individual visitor; to notify you about updates to the site; and to contact you for marketing purposes. If you provide us with your e-mail address(es) during the process of submitting your request, we may use those addresses to send you messages relating to the services provided on this site; We will not use your address(es) for any other purpose. We will not sell or lease any list of addresses we collect to third-parties.

If you provide us with your telephone number(s), we will only use that number to contact you with information regarding our services. While we do not require that you provide telephone numbers, we strongly encourage it so that we can provide you with the most complete service possible.
